KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER /
MARKETING & PROBLEM SOLVER



PERSONAL SKILLS

- Relationship Management
- · Problem-Solving
- Sales & Marketing
- Project Management
- Team Management

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails (Ruby)
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite & PostgreSQL
- GitHub

LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

INTERESTS

- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)
- Weight Training
- American Football
- Specialty Coffee

CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

- My Portfolio: https://keiichi031605.github.io/ keiichi-portfolio/

- Linkedin: keiichi katsuno

- GitHub: keiichi031605

PROFILE

A Coffee & Tech Enthusiast. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about creating a solution for business improvement. Enjoying working & living in a new environment with new technology.

Marketing, Relationship Management and Production Management over the world for the past 6+ years. This journey has given me confidence to collaborate with diverse people. I'm competent in Team Management and Teamwork, and proud of my emotional awareness for solving the problems as well as meeting the needs.

PROJECT

"WHATSPOT" (SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICE)

- The mobile app that you can share any places or recommendations with your friends so that you get more reliable information.

URL: https://www.whatsthespot.com (Built in Ruby on rails)

EXPERIENCE

QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST

InverCafé Ltda., Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (Internship)

- Quality Assessment of Harvested Green Coffee Products
- Developed: "Deep Industrial Knowledge" / "Marketing"

PRODUCTION MANAGER

The Roasting Shed Co., London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019 (Full-time)

Production Management of Specialty Coffee Products

- Developed: "Production Analysis / "Marketing"

RELATIONSHIP MANAGER

Yuasa Trading Co., Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017 (Full-time)

Business Partnership Management and Account & Order Management - Developed: "Sales & Marketing" / "Project Management" / "Negotiation",

Focused on solving the problems of partners, doubling my area sales targets within a 12-month period.

EDUCATION

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT, COMPUTER SCIENCE

Le Wagon Melbourne | Apr 2020 - June 2020

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, SPORTS MANAGEMENT

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

Outside of study, engaged in American Football club, learning Organisational Theory & Team Management and Logical & Critical Thinking for organisational success